KWANG CHO

Kayco702@gmail.com 9260 Night Mesa St. Las Vegas NV, 89178 702-354-6437

OBJECTIVES

I graduated from Excelsior College in 2020 spring with a degree in Information Technology with a concentration in Cyber Security. My goal is to expand my knowledge and experience in Information Technology to enter the network technology field with mastering network automation. Currently, I am certified CCNA and preparing for CCNP enterprise certifications to increase my knowledge in a constantly evolving network technology. With your current opportunity, I believe that I can expand my career in the Information Technology industry.

EDUCATION

UNLV 2002

Completed 2 years - Biology, concentration on pre-medicine (transfer to Excelsior college)

Excelsior College 2017

Completed 4 years – Bachelor of Science in Information Technology (Concentration on Cybersecurity) graduated: Spring of 2020

Military 2002 - 2012

Completed 10 years – completed various leadership, teamwork, managing, and response to the crisis training / classes

Certifications

Completed – CCNA routing and switching: June of 2021

Preparation – CCNP enterprise projected to achieve these certifications within a year, projected completion June 2022.

EXPERIENCE

Three Turnberry Place | 2747 Paradise rd. Las Vegas NV, 89109 Lead Valet January 2006 – present

Managing Valet, assist front desk/engineering dept., basic desktop support to front desk/engineering dept. maintaining basic networks and accomplishing few IT projects for engineering dept.,

Turnberry Limo | 2857 Paradise rd. Las Vegas NV, 89109 Driver April 2013 – present

Resident service with limo driving, maintaining office PC and setting up backups systems

Army National Guard, Nevada | Nevada state (Las Vegas Team leader/group leader December 2002 – December 2012

Highest position achieved as acting Platoon leader for 16 months. Attended various leadership course and training sessions.

SKILLS

- Leadership training received from military and Three Turnberry Place
- Teamwork course training and course within the military and Three Turnberry Place training course
- Basic knowledges with
 - CCNA fundamental knowledge with routing and switching
 - Network and topology
 - Familiar with basic AWS
 - Currently learning basic operation of Linux
 - Information Technology industry standards and structures
 - Cyber-security basic ethical hacking procedures with KALI Linux

REFERENCES

Charles Lim (702-324-3324) Personal friend (20yrs of relationship)

ve

Ronald Donker (702-732-0110) Turnberry Limo Manager (8yrs of relationship)

Cachanta Pressely (702-809-8014)
Three Turnberry place senior front desk representative (12yrs of relationship)